export default {
    en: {
        ssoSystem: "Nextflow SSO system",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Version {} (alpha)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Copyright © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. All rights reserved.",
    },
    zh: {
        ssoSystem: "Nextflow SSO 系统",
        ssoSystemVersion: "版本 {} (alpha)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "版权所有 © {} Nextflow 云技术。保留所有权利。",
    },
    ko: {
        ssoSystem: "Nextflow SSO 시스템",
        ssoSystemVersion: "버전 {} (알파)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "저작권 © {} Nextflow 클라우드 기술. 모든 권리를 보유합니다.",
    },
    ja: {
        ssoSystem: "Nextflow SSO システム",
        ssoSystemVersion: "バージョン {} (アルファ)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "著作権 © {} Nextflow クラウドテクノロジー。すべての権利を保留します。",
    },
    ru: {
        ssoSystem: "Система SSO Nextflow",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Версия {} (альфа)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Авторское право © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Все права защищены.",
    },
    es: {
        ssoSystem: "Sistema SSO Nextflow",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Versión {} (alfa)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Derechos de autor © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Todos los derechos reservados.",
    },
    fr: {
        ssoSystem: "Système SSO Nextflow",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Version {} (alpha)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Droits d'auteur © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Tous droits réservés.",
    },
    de: {
        ssoSystem: "Nextflow SSO-System",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Version {} (Alpha)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Urheber © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Alle Rechte vorbehalten.",
    },
    it: {
        ssoSystem: "Sistema SSO Nextflow",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Versione {} (alpha)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Diritti d'autore © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Tutti i diritti riservati.",
    },
    pt: {
        ssoSystem: "Sistema SSO Nextflow",
        ssoSystemVersion: "Versão {} (alfa)",
        ssoSystemCopyright: "Direitos autorais © {} Nextflow Cloud Technologies. Todos os direitos reservados.",
    },
};
